<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Movie DB</string>
    <string name="movies_menu">Movies</string>
    <string name="tv_show_menu">TV Show</string>
    <string name="popular_people_menu">Popular People</string>
    <string-array name="submenus">
        <item>Top Rated</item>
        <item>Upcoming</item>
        <item>Now Playing</item>
        <item>Popular</item>
    </string-array>
    <string-array name="submenus_image">
        <item>cinema_pop_corn_popcorn_movies_svgrepo_com</item>
        <item>cinema_glasses</item>
        <item>cinema</item>
        <item>cinema_hd</item>
    </string-array>
    <string name="movie_poster_image">movie poster image</string>
    <string name="background_movie_image">Background Movie Image</string>
    <string name="movie_title">Movie Title</string>
    <string name="movie_description">Movie Description yang panjang banget soalnya mesti diisi pake deskripsi</string>
    <string name="small_movie_image">Small Movie Image</string>
    <string-array name="argylle">
        <item>Argylle</item>
        <item>When the plots of reclusive author Elly Conway\'s fictional espionage novels begin to mirror the covert actions of a real-life spy organization, quiet evenings at home become a thing of the past. Accompanied by her cat Alfie and Aiden, a cat-allergic spy, Elly races across the world to stay one step ahead of the killers as the line between Conway\'s fictional world and her real one begins to blur.</item>
    </string-array>
    <string-array name="batman_v_superman">
        <item>Batman V Superman: Dawn of Justice</item>
        <item>Fearing the actions of a god-like Super Hero left unchecked, Gotham City’s own formidable, forceful vigilante takes on Metropolis’s most revered, modern-day savior, while the world wrestles with what sort of hero it really needs. And with Batman and Superman at war with one another, a new threat quickly arises, putting mankind in greater danger than it’s ever known before.</item>
    </string-array>
    <string-array name="interstellar">
        <item>Interstellar</item>
        <item>The adventures of a group of explorers who make use of a newly discovered wormhole to surpass the limitations on human space travel and conquer the vast distances involved in an interstellar voyage.</item>
    </string-array>
    <string-array name="migration">
        <item>Migration</item>
        <item>After a migrating duck family alights on their pond with thrilling tales of far-flung places, the Mallard family embarks on a family road trip, from New England, to New York City, to tropical Jamaica.</item>
    </string-array>
    <string-array name="star_wars">
        <item>Star Wars: The Empire Strikes Back</item>
        <item>The epic saga continues as Luke Skywalker, in hopes of defeating the evil Galactic Empire, learns the ways of the Jedi from aging master Yoda. But Darth Vader is more determined than ever to capture Luke. Meanwhile, rebel leader Princess Leia, cocky Han Solo, Chewbacca, and droids C-3PO and R2-D2 are thrown into various stages of capture, betrayal and despair.</item>
    </string-array>
    <string-array name="the_beekeeper">
        <item>The Beekeeper</item>
        <item>One man’s campaign for vengeance takes on national stakes after he is revealed to be a former operative of a powerful and clandestine organization known as Beekeepers.</item>
    </string-array>
    <string-array name="the_dark_knight">
        <item>The Dark Knight</item>
        <item>Batman raises the stakes in his war on crime. With the help of Lt. Jim Gordon and District Attorney Harvey Dent, Batman sets out to dismantle the remaining criminal organizations that plague the streets. The partnership proves to be effective, but they soon find themselves prey to a reign of chaos unleashed by a rising criminal mastermind known to the terrified citizens of Gotham as the Joker.</item>
    </string-array>
    <string-array name="wonder_woman">
        <item>Wonder Woman</item>
        <item>An Amazon princess comes to the world of Man in the grips of the First World War to confront the forces of evil and bring an end to human conflict.</item>
    </string-array>
    <string-array name="wonka">
        <item>Wonka</item>
        <item>Willy Wonka – chock-full of ideas and determined to change the world one delectable bite at a time – is proof that the best things in life begin with a dream, and if you’re lucky enough to meet Willy Wonka, anything is possible.</item>
    </string-array>
</resources>
